(Howard:)Hey, what's up?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Is that my future
daughter-in-law, the doctor?!
(Howard:)No, Ma! It's Raj!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)He's a doctor
too, right?!
(Howard:)Yes!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Like Leonard and
the skinny weirdo!
(Howard:)Sheldon, yes!
(Howard:)Everybody's a doctor but me!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Well, whose fault
is that?!
(Howard:)What's up?
(Raj:)Leonard's putting disgusting
memories in
(Raj:)my memory foam mattress.
(Raj:)Can I stay here tonight?
(Howard:)Sure, but I'm going out
with Bernadette.
(Howard:)It'll just be you and my mother.
(Raj:)I guess that's okay.
(Howard:)Ma, can Rajesh sleep over?!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Of course, he and I
can play doctor!
(Raj:)She's kidding, right?
(Howard:)I don't know, she's pretty
feisty since
(Howard:)they put her on
hormone-replacement therapy.